Guide to the Central Washington University Facilities Management Department, Planning and Construction Files 1954-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Technical Data Collection Files, 1954-1990; II
  - Men’s Residence Hall (Barto), 1962; TD 1812 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - Residence Halls, 1964; TD 1813 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - Residence Hall for Women, 1962; TD 1814 (Box-folder 16-5)
  - Preliminary Report. Hertz Music Hall, 1960; TD 1815 (Box-folder 16-6)
  - Music Building, 1961; TD 1816 (Box-folder 16-7)
  - Mitchell administration Bldg., 1966; TD 1817 (Box-folder 16-8)
  - Language and literature problem, 1973; TD 1818 (Box-folder 16-9)
  - Space analysis administration building, 1963; TD 1819 (Box-folder 16-10)
  - P.E. laboratory addition, 1975; TD 1822 (Box-folder 16-11)
  - Foundation investigation. Fine and applied arts building, 1966; TD 1824 (Box-folder 16-12)
  - Campus historical photos, 1959; TD 1825 (Box-folder 16-13)
  - Energy consumption data, 1983; TD 1828 (Box-folder 16-14)
  - Construction photos – McConnell Remodel, 1980; TD 1836 (Box-folder 16-15)
  - Construction Photos for Wildcat Remodel – Conversion to computer center, 1980; TD 1837 (Box-folder 16-16)
  - Construction Photos for Randall Safety Corrections, TD 1838 (Box-folder 16-17)
  - Courson/Muzzall Heating Analysis, 1983; TD 1844 (Box-folder 16-18)
  - Tomlinson Field Irrigation. Construction Photos, 1983; TD 1862 (Box-folder 16-19)
  - Construction photos. Storm drain, 1983; TD 1863 (Box-folder 16-20)
  - Chestnut/Poplar improvements, 1981; TD 1866 (Box-folder 16-21)
  - Analysis of electrical service and systems in Hebeler Hall, 1983; TD 1870 (Box-folder 16-22)
  - Construction Photos. Sewer, 1983; TD 1871 (Box-folder 16-23)
  - Sewer Rehabilitation. Photos, TD 1872 (Box-folder 16-24)
  - Construction Photos Irrigation Systems, 1973; TD 1875 (Box-folder 16-25)
  - Construction Photos and Diary. for Dean Science ‘redundant’ water service, 1982-1983; TD 1878 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - Regrading of Town Ditch, TD 1885 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - 13 year energy summary, 1971-1984; TD 1919 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - Energy Conservation Correspondence, 1973-1976; TD 1922 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - Energy Conservation Correspondence, 1973-1976; TD 1922 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - Energy survey videotape log, 1985 (Box-folder 17-6)
  - Energy survey videotape log, 1985 (Box-folder 17-7)
  - Survey and analysis of heating, ventilating and air conditioning system, 1985; TD 1926 (Box-folder 17-8)
  - Infrared Survey of academic buildings and steam utilidor, 1985; TD 1931 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - Annual energy consumption and cost, 1985; TD 1932 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - Energy use profile reports, 1984; TD 1932 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - Energy Conservation Correspondence and Materials, 1977-1983; TD 1939 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - Energy Conservation Correspondence and Materials, 1977-1983; TD 1939 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - Design computations for oil storage tanks, 1974; TD 1943 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - Academic water meter statistics, 1971; TD 1950 (Box-folder 18-7)
  - Water use statistics for elements of lang-lit, 1971-1974; TD 1951 (Box-folder 18-8)
  - Water use statistics for housing, 1971-1974; TD 1952 (Box-folder 18-9)
  - Balance report. Nicholson Pavilion, 1985; TD 1954 (Box-folder 18-10)
  - Health center culvert, 1985; TD 1956 (Box-folder 18-11)
  - Edison Hall, Structural adequacy report, 1985; TD 1959 (Box-folder 18-12)
  - Energy Use reports and graphs, 1985; TD 1962 (Box-folder 18-13)
  - Energy Use reports and graphs, 1985; TD 1962 (Box-folder 18-14)
  - Emergency heating and power restrictions, 1974; TD 1966 (Box-folder 18-15)
  - Shaw-Smyser Hall Electrical Load Study, 1986; TD 1969 (Box-folder 19-1)
  - CWU disposal program, 1985; TD 1972 (Box-folder 19-2)
  - Lind Hall. Electrical Load Study, 1986; TD 1979 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - Black Hall Electrical Load Study, 1986; TD 1980 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Barge Hall Electrical load study, 1986; TD 1982 (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Pool enclosure corrosion investigation, 1988; TD 1989 (Box-folder 19-6)
  - Central Washington University Master Plan, 1986; TD 2013 (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Technical Assistance Study of Steam Distribution System, 1989; TD 2015 (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Subsurface explorations and geotechnical engineering analyses for the proposed psychology-animal research facility, 1990; TD 2016 (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Subsurface explorations and geotechnical engineering analyses for the proposed barge hall renovations, 1990; TD 2017 (Box-folder 19-10)
  - Library construction photos, TD 2018 (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Explorations and geotechnical studies, aquatic center, 1988 (Box-folder 19-12)
- Photographs, circa 1980s; III
  This series primarily contains slides, though some negatives and contact sheets are also present. The slides are undated, though they appear to be from the late 1970s and 1980s. Pictured is the conference center--the building and activities in the building. Also included are slides depicting food services, including banquets and events.
  Arranged topically and in original order.
  - Bouillon remodel, “Existing Artwork”, November 1976; TD 1915 (Box-folder 20-1)
  - Slides – Dorms, 1978 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Slides – Residence Halls: Meisner (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Moore (Box-folder 20-4)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – North (Box-folder 20-5)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Munson (Box-folder 20-6)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Quigley (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Short-Getz (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Sparks (Box-folder 20-9)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Stevens Whitney (Box-folder 20-10)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Student Village (Box-folder 20-11)
  - Slides – Residence Halls – Wahle (Box-folder 20-12)
  - Negatives – Residence Halls – Wahle (Box-folder 20-13)
  - Slides – Food Services – Wild Board Dinner (Box-folder 20-14)
  - Slides – Food Services – Depot Deli (Box-folder 20-15)
  - Slides – Food Services – Student Appreciation Day (Box-folder 20-16)
  - Slides – Food Services – Sweetheart Dinner, 1987 (Box-folder 20-17)
  - Slides – Food Services – Wild Board Dinner/Sweeheart Dinner, 1987 (Box-folder 20-18)
  - Slides – Food Services – Food Services Banquet (Box-folder 20-19)
  - Slides – Food Services – Student Appreciation Barbeque (Box-folder 20-20)
  - Negatives and Contact Sheets - Food Services (Box-folder 20-21)
  - Slides – Conference Center (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Football camp (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Outdoors (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Outdoors (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Student Activities (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Indoors (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Slides – Conference Center – People (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Activities (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Slides – Conference Center – Meeting Rooms (Box-folder 21-9)
- Oversized materials, IV
  This series contains reports, plans and drawings, oversized.
  - Proposed bicycle path plan, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Fence modifications (Box 22)
  - Parking lot modifications (Box 22)
  - Campus Maps (Box 22)
  - Electrical Power diagrams (Box 22)
  - Aerial maps (Box 22)
  - Campus plan, 1959 (Box 22)
  - Hebeler playfield modification, 1975 (Box 22)
  - Technology Building (Box 22)
  - Psychology Building (Box 22)
  - Food Facilities Warehouse (Box 22)
  - Language and Literature Building, 1967 (Box 22)